http://www.ppmag.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICYLast Updated November 16, 2015Thank you for visiting PPmag.com, a Web site of Professional Photographers of America (PPA). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this PPA site.The Information We CollectAt PPmag.com, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls, express an opinion, or subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.In certain areas of PPmag.com, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site's activities and offerings.We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer, Safari), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., AOL, AT&T, Earthlink).How We Use the InformationPPA may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs, or services that we believe may be of interest to you.We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a letter to our editors, a posting to a blog or a forum discussion), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us.PPA occasionally shares membership data with selected PPA Affiliate organizations, sponsors and corporate members.We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process (for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena). We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Web site and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements. In addition, we may transfer personally identifiable information about you if we, or one of our business units, are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company.PPA may disclose personally identifiable information to companies whose practices are not covered by this privacy statement (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you. If a site shares personally identifiable information, it will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses either at the point of submission of your personally identifiable information or prior to any such disclosure.We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you have signed up to receive our e-mails and prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided on any marketing e-mail you receive from this site.Finally, PPA will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.Cookies & Web BeaconsTo enhance your experience with PPmag.com, many of our Web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering and creating a user profile on the site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services."Web beacons" or clear .gifs are small pieces of code placed on a Web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a Web page. For example, Web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a Web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. We may use Web beacons on this site from time to time for this and other purposes.Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Ad Servers, and SponsorsPPmag.com contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy policies and notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.PPmag.com uses Google DoubleClick for Publishers to present or serve the advertisements that you may see on PPmag.com. This third-party ad server may use cookies, Web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of this technology by Google DoubleClick for Publishers is subject to its own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy statement.Our Commitment to SecurityWe have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.How You Can Access or Correct InformationAccess to personally identifiable information that is collected from our sites may be accessible for a limited period of time from the point of collection. For example, if you created a password-protected account within our site, you can access that account to review the information you provided.You may also send an e-mail or letter to the following e-mail or street address requesting access to or correction of your personally identifiable information. For verification purposes please include your first name, last name, e-mail address and the password you use for said service.Professional Photographers of America
Marketing & Communications Department
229 Peachtree Street NE, Suite 2200
Atlanta, Georgia 30303
E-mail: csc@ppa.comHow to Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns about the online privacy statement for this site or its implementation you may contact us at csc@ppa.com.Updates & Effective DateFrom time to time, we may update this privacy statement. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.For general information regarding privacy you can visit TRUSTe, BBB Online, or the Federal Trade Commission:https://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.netscape.com
http://www.bbbonline.org/
http://www.ftc.gov/The Privacy Statement posted on this site was last updated on November 16, 2015.© 2015, Professional Photographers of America. All Rights Reserved.
Share
Close
×
